Finding Aid for the Randall Stewart Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- SYNDICATION OF BEATTY"S COLUMN (RICHMOND C.)
  - Stewart, Randall, Sept. 16, 1957 to Coleman Harwell; Sept. 4; 1957 to Coleman Harwell; Sept. 5, 1957 to Harvey Breit; Sept. 5, 1957 to Maurice Dolbier; Oct. 2, 1957 to Raymond Walters, Jr.; Oct. 8, 1957 to Gerald R. Ashford; Oct. 8, 1957 to Mrs. Marion H. Broaddus; Oct. 8, 1957 to Al Lester; Oct. 8, 1957 to Bob Phillips; Oct. 8, 1957 to R. P. Schlabach; Oct. 8, 1957 to Charlotte Walker; Oct: 4, 1957 to Frank Harris; Oct. 3, 1957 to Truman Stacey; Oct. 3, 1957 to Daisy Tucker; Oct. 3, 1957 to Keith Coulbourn; Oct. 3, 1957 to Anna C. Hunter; Oct. 3, 1957 to George A. Doss; Oct. 3, 1957 to Kenneth C. Crabbe; Oct. 3, 1957 to John Fay; Oct. 4, 1957 to B. J. Skelton; Oct. 5, 1957 to Edith Copeland; Nov. 15, 1957 to John E. Drewry; Dec. 3, 1957 to McClure Newspaper Syndicate; Dec. 3, 1957 to King Features Syndicate; Dec. 3, 1957 to NEA Service; Jan. 20, 1958 to Coleman Harwell; March 3, 1958 to Elliott Trimble; n.d. - form letter.
  - Thompson, E. B., Dec. 6, 1957.
- ALLEN TATE PROPOSAL
  - Branscomb, Harvie, n.d.
  - Ransom, John C., March 3, 1959; Feb. 25, (1959).
  - Stewart, Randall, Oct. 1, 1959 to Harvie Branscomb; Sept. 27, 1959 to Tate; Aug. 3, 1959 to Tate.
  - Tate, Allen, Oct. 2, 1959; August 29, 1959 to Henry C. Alexander and Benjamin E. Tate - 2 copies. Aug. 11, 1959; July 30, 1959.
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE
  - Gerber, John C., Jan. 2, 1962.
  - Morison, S.E., March 2, 1932.
  - Pearson, Norman H., Jan. 29, 1953.
  - Whicher, George, Oct. 25, 1951; Oct. 23, 1951 to Houghton Miff lin.:Co.
  - Wills, Jesse, Sept. 28, 1959.
  - George, Dec. 4, 1967, to Mrs. Stewart. Possibly George Core.
- CHRONOLOGICAL LIST OF OUTGOING CORRESPONDENCE
  - to Jesse Wills with enclosures of two letters dated Oct. 25, 1955., Nov. 23, 1955
  - Red (R. P. Warren). F 1., Jan. 25, 1956
  - John C. Ransom. F 1., Jan. 25, 1956
  - John L. Stewart. F 1., Jan. 30, 1956
  - Allen Tate. F 2., Feb. 14, 1956
  - Red (R. P. Warren). F 2., Feb. 14, 1956
  - Andrew Lytle. F 2., Feb. 14, 1956
  - Cleanth Brooks. F 2., Feb. 14, 1956
  - John C. Ransom. F 2., Feb. 14, 1956
  - John C. Ransom. F 2., Feb. 20, 1956.
  - Isabel Howell. F 2., Feb. 26, 1956
  - Allen Tate. F 2., March 6, 1956
  - form letter to Fugitives and inter-locutor critics. F 2., March 6, 1956
  - Robert E. Spiller. F 3., March 7, 1956
  - form letter to Ransom, Davidson, Tate, Warren, Moore, Elliott, Brooks, Lytle. F 3., March 11, 1956
  - John C. Ransom. F 3, March 13, 1956
  - Allen Tate. F 3., March 13, 1956
  - Donald Davidson. F 4., March 14, 1956
  - Red (R. P. Warren). F 4., March 14, 1956
  - Merrill Moore. F 4., March 14, 1956
  - Cleanth Brooks. F 4., March 14, 1956
  - Andrew Lytle. F 4., March 14, 1956
  - William Y. Elliott. F 4., March 14, 1956
  - Willard Thorp. F 4., March 14, 1956
  - Frank Owsley. F 4., March 14, 1956
  - Louise Cowan. F 4., March 14, 1956
  - Robert D. Jacobs. F 4., March 14, 1956
  - William Y. Elliott. F 5., March 22, 1956
  - Merrill Moore. F 5., March 26, 1956
  - Memorandum to Ransom, Davidson, Tate, Warren, Elliott, Wills, Stevenson, Curry, Hirsch, Starr. F 5, March 26, 1956
  - Vincent L. Eaton. F 5., March 29, 1956
  - Virginia Rock. F 5., April 9, 1956
  - Alec B. Stevenson. F 5., April 17, 1956
  - Allen Tate. F 6., April 20, 1956
  - Memorandum to the Chaneellor. F 6., April 20, 1956
  - John C. Ransom. F 6., April 20, 1956
  - Cleanth Brooks. F 6., April 20, 1956
  - Overton Williams, Bursar. F 6., April 20, 1956
  - William Y. Elliott. F 6., April 24, 1956
  - Harold S. Vanderbilt. F 6., April 24, 1956
  - Allen Tate. F 6., April 26, 1956
  - Alec B. Stevenson. F 7., May 1, 1956
  - Harvie Branscomb. F 7., May 7, 1956
  - Mr. and Mrs. Harold S. Vanderbilt. F 7., May 7, 1956
  - Overton Williams. F 7., May 8, 1956
  - Louis Rubin. 2 copies, one with Rubin’s answer. F 7., May 8, 1956
  - Isabel Howell. F 7., May 9, 1956
  - Fannie Cheney. F 7., May 9, 1956
  - Ellen and Jesse Wills. F 7., May 9, 1956
  - Alec B. Stevenson. F 8., May 10, 1956
  - Charles M. Coffin. F 8., May 15, 1956
  - R. E. Amacher. F 8., May 16, 1956
  - Dorothy Bethurum. F 8., May 17, 1956
  - Allen Tate. F 8., May 17, 1956
  - Dr. O. C. Carmichael. Enclosure of 2 copies of letter from Donald Davidson to A. F. Kuhlman dated May 11, 1956. F 8., May 20, 1956
  - LeRoy P. Graf. F 8., May 22, 1956
  - Ralph Morrissey. F 8., May 24, 1956
  - John Marshall. F 8., June 1, 1956
  - John L. Stewart. F 9., June 2, 1956
  - Louis Rubin. F 9., June 2, 1956
  - Louis Rubin. F 9., June 2, 1956
  - John Marshall. F 9., June 4, 1956
  - Louis Rubin. F 9., June 6, 1956
  - John Marshall. F 9., July 5, 1956
  - Louis Rubin. F 10., Sept. 18, 1956
  - Vincent L. Eaton. F 10., Oct. 29, 1956
  - John L. Stewart. F 10., Nov. 30, 1956
  - Louis Rubin. F 10., Dec. 3, 1956
  - Louis Rubin. F 10., Dec. 11, 1956
  - Louis Rubin. F 10., Dec. 17, 1956
  - John Marshall. F 10., Dec. 17, 1956
  - Overton Williams. F 10., Dec. 17, 1956
  - Richmond Beatty. F 11., Feb. 15, 1957
  - Richmond Beatty. F 11., Feb. 22, 1957
  - Joseph. J. Jackson. F 11., Feb. 26, 1957
  - H. Lloyd Stowe. F 11., March 22, 1957
  - Overton Williams. F 11., April 4, 1957
  - H. Lloyd Stowe. F 11., April 4, 1957
  - John Ransom. F 11., April 5, 1957
  - Leonard B. Beach. F 11., May 22 1957
  - Coleman Harwell. F 12., Sept. 4, 1957
  - Harvey Breit. F 12., Sept. 5, 1957
  - Maurice Dolbier. F 12., Sept. 5, 1957
  - Coleman Harwell. F 12., Sept. 16, 1957
  - Louis Rubin. F 12., Sept. 20, 1957
  - John C. Ransom. F 12., Sept. 27, 1957
  - Raymond Walters, Jr. F 12., Oct. 2, 1957
  - John Fay. F 12., Oct. 3, 1957
  - Kenneth C. Crabbe. F 12., Oct. 3, 1957
  - George A. Doss, Jr. F 12½., Oct. 3, 1957
  - Mrs. Anna C. Hunter. F 12½., Oct. 3, 1957
  - Keith Coulborn. F 12½., Oct. 3, 1957
  - Daisy Tucker. F 12½., Oct. 3, 1957
  - Truman Stacy. F 12½., Oct. 3, 1957
  - Frank Harris. F 12½., Oct. 4, 1957
  - A. J. Skelton. F 12½., Oct. 4, 1957
  - Edith Copeland. F 12½., Oct. 5, 1957
  - Gerald R. Ashford. F 12½., Oct. 8, 1957
  - Mrs. Marion H. Broaddus. F L3., Oct. 8, 1957
  - Al Lester. F 13., Oct. 8, 1957
  - Bob Phillips. F 13., Oct. 8, 1957
  - R. P. Schlabach. F 13., Oct. 8, 1957
  - Mrs. Charlotte Walker. F 13, Oct. 8, 1957
  - Allen Tate. F 13., Oct. 24, 1957
  - "Red." (R. P. Warren). F 13., Oct. 24, 1957
  - Louis Rubin. F 13., Nov. 5, 1957
  - Participants in the Fugitive Conference., Nov. 13, 1957
  - Participants in the Fugitive Conference. F 14. With replies from Fugitives. 2 copies. F 14., Nov. 15, 1957
  - Mrs. Frank L. awsley, Sr. F 14., Nov. 15, 1957
  - Mrs. Alfred Starr. F 14., Nov. 15, 1957
  - Mrs. Merrill Moore. F 14., Nov. 15, 1957
  - John E. Drewry. F 14., Nov. 15, 1957
  - NEA Service, Inc. F 15., Dec. 3, 1957
  - King Features Syndicates. F 15., Dec. 3, 1957
  - McClure Newspaper Syndicate. F 15, Dec. 3, 1957
  - Mrs. Merrill Moore. F 15., Dec. 3, 1957
  - William Y. Elliott. F 15., Dec. 9, 1957
  - Louis Rubin. Fr 16. ’, Dec. 16, 1957
  - Harvie Branscomb. F 15., Dec. 19, 1957
  - Allen Tate. F 15., Jan. 10, 1958
  - "Red" (R. P. Warren). F 15., Jan. 10, 1958
  - John C. Ransom. F 15., Jan. 10, 1958
  - Louis Rubin. F 16., Jan. 11, 1958
  - Allen Tate. F 16., Jan. 17, 1958
  - William C. Cobb. F 16., Jan. 17, 1958
  - Coleman Harwell. F 16., Jan. 20, 1958
  - Louis Rubin. F 16., Feb. 1, 1958
  - Donald Ellegood. F 16., April 29, 1958
  - Louis Rubin. F 17., Dec. 3, 1958
  - Louis Rubin. F 17., Dec. 10, 1958
  - John C. Ransom. F 17., Dec. 30, 1958
  - Louis Rubin. F 17., Jan. 6, 1959
  - Marguerite Wriston. F 17., Jan. 12, 1959
  - Allen Tate. F 17., Aug. 3, 1959
  - Allen Tate. F 17., Sept. 27, 1959
  - Chancellor Branscomb. F 17., Oct. 1, 1959
  - form letter to newspaper Editors. F 18. Holograph draft of letter to editors. F 18., Undated